pesa.net.in 2016-06-08

# Welcome to PESA

##  Privacy Policy

We provide marketing tools and services for you to use in your business in order to expand your business. In order to use our products, we require your personal information for instance, your name, your email, your contact number, financial data (credit or debit card details for billing purposes), references (name of the person who refer you to us or his contact number) etc. Such type of information collected from you at the time of joining our business referred as personal information.

We do not share your personal information with any third parties.Some information will be viewable to the registered member who referred you can view your email address, contact number in order to help you to promote your business.

#####  Privacy Statement

Most websites collect personal information. Personal information may for example be collected by website forms, as a result of the use of website services, or through the use of tracking technologies such as cookies. EU data protection law and Indian data privacy law (and similar laws in other jurisdictions) protect individuals from the misuse of their personal information. These laws regulate not just the collection of personal data, but also the storage, use, cross-border transfer, retention and disposal of that data.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that we collect, and the ways in which we use that personal information.

#####  Personal information collection

We may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

• Information about your use of this website (including Name, address, cell phone, Credit/debit details.

• Information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website: email address etc.

• Information about transactions carried out over this website:such as Product purchases.

• Information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services: Audio, video

• Any other information that you send to the company.

#####  Using personal information

We may use your personal information to:

• Administer this website

• When you reach the top earning group, your personal information may be used to inspire others.

• Enable you to access the website and use of the website services.

• Supply products that you purchase.

• Send marketing communications.

We do not disclose your personal information to any third parties, agents or sub-contractors for any purpose.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified above, we may disclose your personal information to the extent that is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

#####  Securing your data

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

We will ensure store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that we collect, and the ways in which we use that personal information. You agree our privacy policy when submitting your personal information on our site. 

We reserve the right to update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.
